John Moors Cabot Papers MS110
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1909 -- 1967; MS110.003; 7.2 Linear Feet
  - Loose Photos: South America, 1953; MS110.003.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Central and South America, 1953 -- 1954; MS110.003.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Central and South America, Poland, 1953 -- 1965; MS110.003.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Sweden, 1954 -- 1957; MS110.003.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Colombia and Guatemala, 1957; MS110.003.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Sweden, 1957; MS110.003.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Central America, Poland Brazil, 1950 -- 1965; MS110.003.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Brazil, 1953 -- 1961; MS110.003.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Colombia, Brazil, Poland, 1957 -- 1962; MS110.003.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Brazil, Poland, 1957 -- 1963; MS110.003.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Brazil and Nicaragua, 1959 -- 1960; MS110.003.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Brazil, 1960; MS110.003.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Brazil, 1959 -- 1961; MS110.003.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Brazil, 1961; MS110.003.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos: Poland, 1962 -- 1966; MS110.003.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Loose Photos, 1952 -- 1961; MS110.003.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Framed Photos: Elizabeth Cabot, Mrs. Roosevelt, Swearing In, 1950 -- 1960; MS110.003.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Framed Photos: Eisenhower, Wooden Horse, 1950 -- 1960; MS110.003.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Framed Photos: War College, Wedding Photo, 1943 -- 1960; MS110.003.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Framed Photos: Tufts Honorary Degree, 1950 -- 1960; MS110.003.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Loose oversized photos, diplomas, signed presidential pictures, drawings, 1953; MS110.003.007.00001 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 7)
    Diplomas from Brazil, Pan American Society of New England; Photos of Buildings; Signed Photos of Truman, Eisenhower, Kennedy, Johnson; drawing of Mr. Cabot in Panama by Zeus (April 16th, 1953, R.DE.P.) and drawing by Freyre, Mexico, DF. 1953.
- Physical Memoribilia, 1924 -- 1966; MS110.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains John Moors Cabot's physical memorabilia. It includes a wooden horse, a wooden bird, metal plates, candleholder, trophies for sports, plaques and medals from the Fletcher School of Diplomacy.
  - John Moors Cabot: Physical Memoribilia, 1924 -- 1966; MS110.004.001 (Box 1)
    Includes a wooden horse, a wooden bird, metal plates, candleholder, trophies for sports, plaques and medals from the Fletcher School of Diplomacy
- Newspaper Clippings, 1939 -- 1980; MS110.005; 4.8 Linear Feet
  This series contains newspaper clippings relating to John Cabot's career.
  This series is arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  - Brazil: Clippings January - June., 1959; MS110.005.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings July 1- July 17., 1959; MS110.005.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings July 18 - July 31., 1959; MS110.005.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings August 1 - 11., 1959; MS110.005.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings August 12-21., 1959; MS110.005.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings August 22-31., 1959; MS110.005.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings September., 1959; MS110.005.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings October 1-15., 1959; MS110.005.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings October 16-17., 1959; MS110.005.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings October 18-31., 1959; MS110.005.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings November - December 16., 1959; MS110.005.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings December 17-31., 1959; MS110.005.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings January 1-11., 1960; MS110.005.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings January 12-22., 1960; MS110.005.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings January 23-31., 1960; MS110.005.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings February - March., 1960; MS110.005.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings April - July 15., 1960; MS110.005.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings July 16 - August 31., 1960; MS110.005.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings September 1-19., 1960; MS110.005.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings September 20 - October 21., 1960; MS110.005.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings October 23-December 31., 1960; MS110.005.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings January., 1961; MS110.005.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings February-March., 1961; MS110.005.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings April-June., 1961; MS110.005.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings July., 1961; MS110.005.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings August 1-15., 1961; MS110.005.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings August 16-31., 1961; MS110.005.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Brazil: Clippings undated, 1961; MS110.005.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Colombia: Clippings May-November 19., 1957; MS110.005.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings November 20-December., 1957; MS110.005.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings Nixon's Visit to Colombia, May 11-13; includes related correspondence from May-June., 1958; MS110.005.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings January-February., 1958; MS110.005.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings March., 1958; MS110.005.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings April., 1958; MS110.005.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings May., 1958; MS110.005.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings June-August., 1958; MS110.005.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Colombia: Clippings September-December, plus related clippings, 1958; MS110.005.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Finland: Clippings, 1950 -- 1951; MS110.005.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Finland: Clippings, 1951 -- 1952; MS110.005.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Finland: Clippings, 1952; MS110.005.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Global Newspapers: Clippings, 1953 -- 1980; MS110.005.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Venezuela Clippings February 7-11., 1953; MS110.005.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Venezuela Clippings February 12-20., 1953; MS110.005.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Clippings February-March., 1953; MS110.005.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Panama Clippings March 27-April 24., 1953; MS110.005.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Cuba Clippings April 3-9., 1953; MS110.005.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Nicaragua Clippings April 7-28., 1953; MS110.005.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: San Salvador Clippings April 20-25., 1953; MS110.005.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Clippings March 31-April 13., 1953; MS110.005.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Clippings April 14-15., 1953; MS110.005.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Clippings April 16-18., 1953; MS110.005.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Clippings April 19-25., 1953; MS110.005.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Clippings April 26-May 31., 1953; MS110.005.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings June., 1953; MS110.005.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 1-2., 1953; MS110.005.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 3-5., 1953; MS110.005.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 6-8., 1953; MS110.005.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 9-15., 1953; MS110.005.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 10., 1953; MS110.005.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 17-18., 1953; MS110.005.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 19-20., 1953; MS110.005.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 21-23., 1953; MS110.005.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Latin America Trip: Milton Eisenhower Clippings July 24-August 8., 1953; MS110.005.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Latin America Trip: Drafts of the Report of Milton Eisenhower Trip August., 1953; MS110.005.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Maria Moors Cabot Prize: Clippings, 1939 -- 1955; MS110.005.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Poland: Clippings December 30-December 31., 1961 -- 1962; MS110.005.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Poland: Clippings, 1963 -- 1965; MS110.005.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Shanghai, China: Clippings, 1948 -- 1949; MS110.005.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Sweden: Clippings February 12-April., 1954; MS110.005.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Sweden: Clippings May-December., 1954; MS110.005.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Sweden: Clippings January-December., 1955; MS110.005.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Sweden: Clippings January-December., 1956; MS110.005.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Sweden: Clippings January-May., 1957; MS110.005.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Washington/Argentina: Clippings, 1945 -- 1946; MS110.005.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Washington, D.C.: Clippings on Latin America September-October 14., 1953; MS110.005.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Washington, D.C.: Clippings on Latin America October 14-December 31., 1953; MS110.005.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Washington, D.C.: Clippings on Latin America January-March., 1954; MS110.005.004.00018 (Box 4)
- Books to be returned, MS110.027.GB (Box 1)